in this video I'll show you how to
在这段视频中 我将向您展示如何
better format a video that's been taken
最好格式化已拍摄的视频
like this in the kind of vertical
像这样在垂直方向上
position and add some blurred sides to
定位并添加一些模糊的边到
it
它
in shotcut so what we're gonna really do
所以我们真正要做的是
is drag and drop this down once to the
就是把这个拖放到
video track and then we're gonna add a
视频曲目 然后我们将添加一个
second instance so I'll right-click and
第二个实例 所以我将右键单击并
go to add video track and I'll do the
转到添加视频曲目 我将执行
same thing I'll go back to the very
同样的事情 我会回到非常
beginning and I'll drag this down again
开始 我会再把它拖下去
so now we have it in duplicate and I
所以现在我们有一式两份 我
only need the audio one so I'm going to
只需要音频的 所以我要
turn off the audio on the second video
关闭第二个视频的音频
track and now when we play we're just
现在 当我们演奏时 我们只是
gonna see what's happening on top of
去看看在上面发生了什么
this first video track all right and
这首视频曲目很好
then back below we'll just see we can't
然后回到下面 我们就会发现我们不能
really see what's happening underneath
真正看到了下面发生的事情
let's take our let's go to the bottom
让我们带着我们的 让我们一起去底层
one and let's go to filters and let's
一 让我们转到过滤器 让我们
just add a size and position filter so
只需添加一个大小和位置过滤器即可
we'll add size and position on here and
我们会在这里增加尺寸和位置 然后
then all of a sudden we see it goes over
然后突然我们看到它过去了
to this black area so we can see if we
到这个黑色区域 所以我们可以看看我们是否
move this it it goes behind this one so
移动这个 它在这个后面 所以
we're manipulating the bottom track
我们正在操纵底部轨道
right now well all we have to do is take
现在我们要做的就是
and go to distort is what we want on the
而去扭曲就是我们想要的
size mode and then when that's done
尺寸模式 然后在该模式完成后
we'll apply a blur so we'll apply this
我们将应用模糊 因此我们将应用此
like a will do blur and we'll do with a
就像遗嘱做模糊一样 我们会用一个
Gaussian blur Gaussian and we'll turn
高斯模糊高斯 我们将转向
that up so it's quite blurry on the
所以它在上面是很模糊的
sides there and now when we play this it
当我们在那里和现在玩这个游戏的时候
will kind of play through and we see
将会发挥作用 我们会看到
what's happening on the side like easier
一边发生的事情就像是更容易
way to do it and then we could even take
做得很好 然后我们甚至可以
this original top one and apply a kind
这是原创的顶层 并应用了一种
of a crop to it so we can add a size and
这样我们就可以增加它的大小
position here and we can just scale it
定位在这里 我们只需扩展即可
so it's not really going to be we're
所以我们不会真的
gonna be moving it towards the center
会把它移到中心
and we'll really just make this a little
我们真的会让这件事变得有点
bit larger so instead of really doing a
大一点 所以不是真的做一个
crop what we're really doing is just
裁剪我们真正在做的只是
kind of making this a little bit larger
把这件事做得有点大了
here and depending on your video you
在这里 根据您的视频
could kind of adjust it too but see
也可以调整一下 但看看
there's a lot of space up on the top
顶部有很多空间
that's kind of wasted there so I might
在那里有点浪费所以我可能
enlarge that sort of like this and then
像这样放大 然后
put it back to the center I could have
把它放回我本可以的中心
also used the edge crop for that and now
现在也使用了边缘裁剪
when we go through and play this it's
当我们浏览并播放这个时
going to look sort of like this and then
看起来有点像这样 然后
when I render this out it's going to be
当我呈现出来时 它将是
much it's gonna have much smoother
它会变得更加顺利
playback it's just a little bit
回放只是一点点
right now because I'm dating it in an
因为我正在与它约会
online software but to render it I would
在线软件 但要渲染它 我会
just click on export go to export file
只需点击“出口”前往“出口”文件
and then choose the location on my
然后选择我的位置
computer where I want to export this but
我想在计算机上输出这个 但
that's basically a quick look at adding
这基本上是快速添加
in these blurred edges and kind of
在这些模糊的边缘和有点
reframing a video that'll have take up
重新构建将占用的视频
the full area instead of having those
整个区域 而不是拥有那些
black bars on the side hopefully found
希望找到侧面的黑条
them formative thanks for watching catch
感谢观看接球比赛 他们形成了影响力
you in the next video
下一个视频中的你